A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, International Program in Health Care Policy (IHP), SG 3, Series 14 FA1475
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, International Program in Health Care Policy, (IHP), SG 3, Series 14
1925-2006
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1475
79.93 Cubic Feet 189 letter-size document boxes, 15 legal size document boxes,
Arrangement
Arranged in ten subseries as follows:
1. IHP Chronological Files
2. IHP Reference
3. Harkness Fellowships Administration
4. IHP Financial Administration
5. President's Discretionary Fund (PDF)
6. Symposiums and Surveys
7. Ian Axford (New Zealand) Fellowships in Public Policy
8. Atlantic Fellowships
9. IHP Program Files
10. Audiovisual Materials
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Scope and Contents
This series documents the administration of the International Program in Health Care Policy (IHP) including records documenting symposiums, conferences and workshops, program planning, correspondence and reports and chronological files, as well as records of the associated fellowship programs including the Harkness Fellowships, Atlantic Fellowships and Ian Axford (New Zealand) Fellowships. The bulk of the material represented in this series spans the 1990s through the early 2000s.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. The initial transfer of archival records to RAC began in 1986, and transfers continue on a regular basis. This series was transferred to RAC as multiple accessions from 2007 through 2009.
- International Program in Health Care Policy (IHP), 1925-2006; 14
  - IHP Chronological Files, 1
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1998 August - In (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1998 August - Out (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1998 September - In (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1998 September - Out (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1998 October - In (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1998 October - Out (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1998 November - In (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1998 November - Out (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1998 December - In (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1998 December - Out (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 January - In (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 January - Out (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 January - Out (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 February - In (Box 3, Folder 2-4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 February - Out (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 March - In (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 March - Out (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 March - Out (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 April - In (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 April - Out (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 May - In (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 May - Out (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 May - Out (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 June - In (Box 8, Folder 4-5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 June - Out (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 July - In (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 1999 July - Out (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 January - In (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 February - In (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 February - In (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 February - Out (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 March - In (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 March - In (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 March - Out (Box 26, Folder 3-5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 March - Out (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 April - In (Box 27, Folder 2-4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 April - Out (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 April - Out (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 May - In (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 May - In (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 May - Out (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 May - Out (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 June - In (Box 30, Folder 3-5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 June - Out (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 July - In (Box 31, Folder 4-5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 July - In (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 July - Out (Box 32, Folder 3-4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 July - Out (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 August - In (Box 33, Folder 3-5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 August - In (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 August - Out (Box 34, Folder 2-5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 August - Out (Box 35, Folder 1-3)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 September - In (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 September - In (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 September - Out (Box 36, Folder 2-4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 September - Out (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 October - In (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 October-December - Out (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 October - Out (Box 39, Folder 2-5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 January - Out (Box 60, Folder 4-5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 January - Out (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 November - In (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 November - Out (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 December - In (Box 63, Folder 4-5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2000 December - Out (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2001 January - In (Box 64, Folder 3-4)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2001 January - Out (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - IHP Chronological Files - 2001 January - Out (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
  - IHP Reference, 2
    - Brookings Briefing Book - 1991 Harkness Fellows - Washington Seminar on Understanding American Politics, Washington, D. C., 1991 November 16-21 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Brookings Briefing Book - 1992 Harkness Fellows - Washington Seminar on Understanding American Politics, Washington, D. C., 1992 November 16-18 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Brookings Briefing Book - 1994 Harkness Fellows - Washington Seminar on Understanding American Politics, Washington, D. C., 1994 February 23-25 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Brookings Briefing Book - 1995 Harkness Fellows - Washington Seminar on Understanding American Politics, Washington, D. C., 1995 February 8-10 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Brookings Briefing Book - 1995-1996 Harkness Fellows - Washington Seminar on Understanding American Politics, Washington, D. C., 1996 February 6-9 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Brookings Briefing Book - 1996-1997 Harkness Fellows - Washington Seminar on Understanding American Politics, Washington, D. C., 1997 February 5-8 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Brookings Briefing Book - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Washington Seminar on Understanding American Politics, Washington, D. C., 1998 February 25-27 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Harkness Employment Conference - "Employment and the Future of Work", Edited by Gary Hawke, 1995 May 9-10 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Democracy in America, Alexis de Tocqueville, 1966 (1988) (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - The Smart Voters Guide to Welfare, Welfare Reform in California, Eugene Smolensky (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - The Smart Voters Guide to Health Care Reform, Dwayne Bank (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Harkness Health Conference - Health Policy: International Comparisons and Special Issues, 1993 December (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings of Josiah Macy Jr. Foundation Conferences, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Murdoch, by William Shawcross (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Outcome Funding: A New Approach to Public Sector Grantmaking, by Williams and Webb, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - The Ships of the Ancient Near East (c. 2000-500 B.C.), by Marie-Christine De Graeve, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Crime Prevention in America: A British Perspective, by Jon Bright (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - The Design of Acute General Hospitals, by R. R. Scrymgour, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Unlocking the Imagination by Simon Duffy, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Better Cities for Better Education, Better Education for Better Cities, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Swan Songs Poems, by Sue Lenier, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Process Tracing in Clinical Judgement: An Analytical Approach, Dissertation by Robin Miles Hogarth, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - A Survey of Interphase Reaction and Exchange in Fixed and Moving Beds, by Beveridge, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - People in Cities: A Transatlantic Policy Exchange, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Delirious New York, by Rem Koolhaus, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Fighting Leviathan: Building Social Markets that Work, by Howard Davies, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Truimph of the Nomads: A History of Ancient Australia, by Geoffrey Blainey, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Cruel, Poor and Brutal Nations, by John Cawte, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Science and the Quiet Art: The Role of Medical Research in Health Care, by David Weatherall, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Report of a Study of Land Use Patterns in the United States, by Kenneth Sargent (Commonwealth Fund Fellowship, 1957-1958) (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Australia - Long Term Care - Articles, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 2-4)
    - Australia - Long Term Care - Articles, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Sweden - Long Term Care - Articles (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Germany - Long Term Care - Articles (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - United States - Long Term Care - Articles, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Denmark - Long Term Care - Articles, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - United Kingdom - Long Term Care - Articles (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - 1999 Cross National Comparison of Health Data Systems - Chart Book (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Harkness Fellows is Health Policy - Brochure 2000-2001 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Guidelines for 1999-2000 Harkness Fellowships (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Harkness Fellowships - Famous Fellows, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - 2000-2001 Harkness Fellowships - List of Suggested Projects and Comments (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - 1999-2000 Harkness Fellowships - List of Suggested Projects (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Handbook for Harkness Fellows 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Red Book University (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Coast to Coast, by James Morris, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Harkness Health Conference - Health Policy: International Comparisons and Special Issues, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Directory of Commonwealth Fund and Harkness Fellows, 1925-1990 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Democracy in America, by Alexis de Tocqueville (Abridged), 1981 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Democracy in America, by Alexis de Tocqueville (Translated by George Lawrence) (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - The Cold War: A History, by Martin Walker, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - The New Machine Men, by Stephen Mills, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - The Penguin History of the United States, by Hugh Brogran (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Changing Places, by David Lodge, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Algeria: The Next Fundamentalist State, by Graham E. Fuller (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - 1996 Atlantic Fellowships - Handbook and Directory (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Harkness Bulletins, 1995-1997 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows Orientation Seminar, 1998 September 22-25 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - 1995 Harkness Fellowships - Reference Guide (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - 1996 Harkness Fellowships - Reference Guide (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships - Handbook (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - 1997 Atlantic Fellowships - Handbook and Directory (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Commonwealth Fund - Five Year Outlook, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Fifty Years of Ideas in Health Care Building, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Up Against the Wall, America, by Craig McGregor, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Reforming Culture: American Lessons, by Simon Crine (Fabian Society Pamphlet 567), 1999 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Indiana University Center on Philanthropy - Essays on Philanthropy, No. 11 and No. 12, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - New Zealand - Long Term Care - Articles, 1990s (Box 79, Folder 4-7)
    - New Zealand - Long Term Care - Articles, 1990s (Box 80, Folder 1-5)
    - United States - Long Term Care - Articles, 1990s (Box 83, Folder 1-4)
    - Canada - Long Term Care - Articles, 1985-2001 (Box 84, Folder 1-3)
    - International Book Publishing: An Encyclopedia, Atlbacha and Hoshino (Box 187)
    - Media Studies Journal: Media and Congress, 1996 Winter (Box 187)
    - Media Studies Journal: Defining Moments in Journalism, 1997 Spring (Box 187)
    - The Australian Coordinated Care Trials: Methodological Issues in Trial Design and Evaluation, 1999 (Box 187)
    - The Australian Coordinated Care Trials: Background and Trial Descriptions, 1999 (Box 187)
    - The Australian Coordinated Care Trials: Interim National Evaluations Summary, 1999 September (Box 187)
    - Informing the Future: Critical Issues in Health, Institute of Medicine (IOM), 2000 (Box 188)
    - Media Studies Journal: 1968, 1998 Fall (Box 188)
    - Media Studies Journal: What's Next, 1999 Spring-Summer (Box 188)
    - Journal of Policy Analysis Management, Journal 19, Number 4, 2000 Fall (Box 188)
    - Journal of Policy Analysis Management, Volume 20, Number 1, 2001 Winter (Box 188)
    - Journal of Policy Analysis Management, Volume 20, Number 2, 2001 Spring (Box 188)
    - Commonwealth Fund Directory of British (1925-1955) and Continental Fellows (1952-1955), 1925-1955 (Box 188)
    - Fourth Health Services and Policy Research Conference, Canberra, 2005 November 13-16 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting, 2001 January (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Health Articles - Canada, New Zealand, Australia, 2006 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - First Nations and Inuit Health Branch, Canada, 2003 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Harkness Fellowships in Health Care Policy Meeting, 2003 May 16 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Medical Expenditure Panel Survey, AHRQ (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Robin Osborn's Email's and Notes, 2005-2006 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - State and Territory Highlights - Improving Patient Safety, 2005 July (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - National Health Service (NHS) - Articles, Surveys and Reports, 2005-2006 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Robin Osborn's Email's and Notes, 2005-2006 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Australian Government Department of Health and Ageing System: Concise Factbook, and Related Materials, 2006 January (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Health Canada - A Statistical Profile of the Health of First Nations in Canada, 2003 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Harkness Fellows Press Clippings, 1990-1996 (Box 195, Folder 1-4)
  - Harkness Fellowships Administration, 3
    - Harkness Questionnaires, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 1997 Harkness Nominator File (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Confidential material
    - 1996 Harkness Fellowships - Thompson, James (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 1996 Harkness Fellowships - Thompson, James (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 1996 Harkness Fellowships - Wilson, William (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - 1996 Harkness Fellowships - Wilson, William (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - 1996 Harkness Fellowships - Slade, Christina (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - 1996 Harkness Fellowships - Slade, Christina (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - 1996 Harkness Fellowships - Shickle, Darren (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - 1996 Harkness Fellowships - Shickle, Darren (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships - Brochure Materials (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships - Promotional Materials (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships - Application Materials (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - 1998 Harkness Fellowships - Application Materials (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellowships - 1999 Mid-Year Reporting Seminar (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellowships - List of Suggested Projects (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellowships - Final Reporting Seminar (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellowships - Biographies (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellows - Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation Meetings, London (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation Mailings (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation - New York City (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation - Dinner (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation Seminar - Speaker Biographies (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation Material (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation - Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation - Invitations (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation, Washington, D. C., 1998 October 19-21 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation, New York, 1998 December 2-4 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Travel Requests (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - 1960-1997 Harkness Fellows (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Harkness Fellowships - Final Reports by Fellows (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellowships - Bibliographies (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Interim Reports (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellowships - Extension Support Letters (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellowships - AUS, NZ, UK - Guidelines (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Budget (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellowships - Interim Reports (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellowships - Interim Reports (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellowships - Administrative Duties for Host Institutions (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation Evaluations (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellowships - Interim Reports (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation Evaluation, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellowships - Harkness Fellows and Mentors (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - 1997-1998 Brookings Seminar - Hotel (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - 1997-1998 Brookings Seminar - Planning (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - 1997-1998 Brookings Seminar - Evaluations (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellowships - Harkness Final Reporting Seminar - Planning (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Brookings Meeting, 1998 February 27 (Box 42, Folder 3-4)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Basnett, Ian - Final Report (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Basnett, Ian (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Claxton, Karl (Box 43, Folder 3-5)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Claxton, Karl - Final Report (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Cohen, David (Box 44, Folder 2-3)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Cohen, David - Final Report (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Coker, Richard (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Coker, Richard (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Coker, Richard - Final Report, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Esmail, Aneez (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Esmail, Aneez - Final Report (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Ezard, Nadine - Final Report (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Ezard, Nadine (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Harrison, Kay (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Harrison, Kay - Final Report (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Lipman, Mark (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - McKenzie, Kwame (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - McKenzie, Kwame - Final Report (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Rylance, John (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Smellie, Patrick (Box 47, Folder 2-3)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Smellie, Patrick - Final Report (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Vallance, Sarah (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Vallance, Sarah (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Wilkinson, Helen (Box 48, Folder 3-4)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Wilkinson, Helen - Final Report (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Wilson, Carlene (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellowships - Marketing (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellowships - UK Marketing (Box 49, Folder 2-3)
    - 1994-1995 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports (Box 94, Folder 1-4)
    - 1994-1995 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports (Box 95, Folder 1-4)
    - 1994-1995 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports (Box 96, Folder 1-4)
    - 1995-1996 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports (Box 97, Folder 1-4)
    - 1995-1996 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports (Box 98, Folder 1-4)
    - 1995-1996 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports (Box 99, Folder 1-4)
    - 1998 Harkness Fellows - Mentors Correspondence (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Budget (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - 1997-1998 Harkness Fellows - Orientation Materials (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 110, Folder 1-5)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 111, Folder 1-3)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports (Box 111, Folder 4-5)
    - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellows - Interim Reports (Box 112, Folder 1-3)
    - Public Relations Program to Support the Harkness Fellows, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Selected Press Clippings Commonwealth Fund Programs, 1992 November-1993 March (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Plowden Press Release Comments, 1988 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - 1990 Harkness Fellows Outcomes, 1992-1996 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - 1991 Harkness Fellows Outcomes, 1992-1997 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - 1992 Harkness Fellows Outcomes, 1992-1997 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - 1993 Harkness Fellows Outcomes, 1993-1996 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - 1994 Harkness Fellows Outcomes (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - 1995 Harkness Fellows Outcomes, 1995-1997 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - 1996 Harkness Fellows Outcomes, 1996-1997 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - 2000-2001 Harkness Fellowships in Health Care Policy - Orientation Seminar, New York, NY, 2000 September 25-28 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - 2002-2003 Harkness Fellowships in Health Care Policy - Orientation Seminar, New York, NY, 2002 September 9-12 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - 2002-2003 Harkness Fellowships in Health Care Policy - Orientation Seminar, New York, NY, 2002 September 9-12 (Box 130, Folder 1)